free-management-ebooks.com 2013-06-30

# Free Management eBooks - Privacy Policy

Our newsletter will be sent to you twice a month. 

It will keep you informed about any new eBooks we release as well as any new resources that will help you with your personal development.

We know your time is precious, so it will be short, specific and relevant.

Your details will not be passed on to any third parties and you can unsubscribe at anytime. 

We also collect data that allows us to remember you, any interests that you have recorded and how you use this website. This saves you from re-keying information when you return to the site and allows us to arrange our website content to match your preferred interests.

We use 'cookies' to collect this data. Cookies are text-only strings of information that are stored on your web browser or hard disk. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings of your web browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive facilities of our site if cookies are disabled.

Further details are available on our **Cookie Policy** or for further information about how to disable cookies in your browser please visit the [**About Cookies Website**](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

Your IP address (this is your computer's individual identification number for internet connection) that is automatically logged by our web server. This is used to note your interest in our website.

Your preferences and use of email updates that are recorded by emails we send you (only if you have selected to receive email updates).  

By using the website you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. As a general rule, no personal information (i.e. name, address, telephone number, e-mail address) is automatically collected from users of this website. However, there may be circumstances in which users voluntarily supply such information and in this event, any such information will be kept secure and confidential and will be used only for those purposes made known to users at the time the information is collected, or for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy. We will also add your registered email address and personal details to our database if you register for updates via Facebook. We follow strict security procedures for the storage and disclosure of information you have given us in order to prevent unauthorised access.

When we include links to other internet sites, on this site and in our newsletters and other communications, we do so solely as a convenience to our visitors. Operators of such linked sites may acquire personal information about you through registration procedures or other means and may use that information in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control. Your access and use of linked sites is solely at your own risk.

Whenever we obtain your personal information we take reasonable precautions to protect it from unauthorised access or disclosure, but we cannot act as insurers of the security of your personal information transmitted over the internet. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorised third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or missions beyond our reasonable control. 

**Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice**  
This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the 'effective date' below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of this website constitutes your agreement to this. 

**Date Last Modified:**  
This Privacy Notice was last modified May 1, 2013

**Contact Information:**  
Please contact the us with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice using this email address webmaster@free-management-ebooks.com.
